ingrambook.com 2015-06-22

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated March 9, 2015

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The name, address, e-mail, and any payment information provided by You to Ingram Book Group Inc.  ("Ingram"), together with information regarding the manner in of use via this Site, will not be processed or disclosed by us to third parties except as permitted by this Privacy Policy or as we believe is reasonably permitted by law or regulation.

Our registration and user forms require users to provide us with information, including your name and e-mail address.  The forms allow you to request additional information or order our Products or additional material as may be available from Ingram.  This information falls into two categories: Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) and Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”) (collectively “Information”).  PII includes information that identifies you specifically, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, other contact information, employer, business name, social security number and credit card numbers.  Non-PII is anonymous data that does not identify you specifically, such as aggregate data about the number of people who have accessed a particular Product.  We may collect, use, transfer and disclose Non-PII for any purpose. You can choose not to provide PII we may request of you, but, in general, most of the PII we request is required in order to provide our service and the lack of such PII will prevent us from doing so.

When you browse any Ingram website, you do not do so anonymously.  Other information to be collected and logged includes: browser type, browser language, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address and domain, date and time of your request, and the device you are using.  This aggregate information is used to properly administer our products, make updates to our website, and analyze how our site is being used. 

**Ingram’s Use Of Your Information**    
Ingram uses your Information by itself or in conjunction with data collected through other sources to meet our contractual commitments to you, to provide the Products to you, to respond to your requests, to properly administer and maintain the products, to customize content supplied to you, to provide you with information related to the products, to update the website and analyze how it is used, to offer you the product, to improve the products, to prevent fraud, violation of intellectual property rights and unauthorized use of products or your account, to track your purchase history, to conduct research, to contact you, to inform you about certain changes to our products, to develop new products, or as otherwise appropriate to the business needs of Ingram related to the products.  If you no longer use the products, Ingram may retain any information that you have provided and may continue to use it for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

**Content Owners**  
Ingram may share information about you and your use of the products with content owners or licensees that have rights related to the products that you access (“Content Owners”).  Content Owners will use this information for their own research and tracking purposes, to evaluate product use and access, to improve products and related analysis.  Ingram will not reveal your PII to Content Owners, just anonymous product usage data that does not identify you specifically. 

**Disclosures As Required By Law Or To Prevent Harm**    
Ingram reserves the right to disclose information if we reasonably believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable terms of use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address illegal or suspected illegal activities, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Ingram, its users, the Content Owners or the public as required or permitted by law.

**Children's Privacy**  
You must be 18 years of age or older to create an account on this website.  Ingram does not knowingly solicit orders or collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen.  If we have reason to believe that any personally identifying information has been submitted to us by a child under thirteen, contact us and we will delete that information as soon as possible.   We will not disclose that information to any third party or use it ourselves in any way.

**Cookies**  
This Site employs "cookies" to speed navigation of the site, recognize each User and his or her access privileges, and track a User's site usage.  Ingram uses cookies so that it may customize the site for your use. A cookie is a series of data characters that, when programmed into a site, is placed by the web server into the browser's application folder on your computer and will allow this Site to associate you with your information.  Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. A User can set his or her browser to refuse cookies, but the User may not be able to use all functions within Ingram if cookies are disabled. Certain applications on this Site require cookies to function correctly, such as the shopping cart and buyback quotes.  The Ingram cookies do not have the capability of infiltrating a User's hard drive and gathering a User's personal and confidential business information.

**Google Analytics**

Ingram uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google") to help us improve our site. Google Analytics uses cookies which are persistent in nature to help analyze how users navigate this Site.

The table below explains the Google Analytics cookies we use and why we use them.

**Cookie Source**

| 

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Function**

| 

**Expiry Date**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Google Analytics

| 

_utmt  
_utma   
_utmb   
_utmc   
_utmz

| 

These cookies belong to third parties and are used to collect information on how visitors use this site. Collected information is used to compile reports and to help improving the site. The cookies collect information in an anonym way, including (i) the number of visitors to the site, (ii) where visitors have come to this site from and (iii) the pages of this site they visited. [ _Click here for an overview of privacy at Google_](http://t.signaledue.com/e1t/c/5/f18dQhb0S7lC8dDMPbW2n0x6l2B9nMJW7t5XYg4Xr0_CW2BgXCY8q-qn6W7dKLV856dFPWf1ZPm9T02?t=http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html&si=6118029987938304&pi=e3dd71cb-d2e4-4500-97f5-1ac82039fb60 "External link").

| 

_utmt expires 10 minutes after your visit

_utma: 2 years from the date that it was set   
_utmb: 30 mins from the date that it was set   
_utmc: end of session/close of browser   
_utmz: 6 months from the date that it was set  

Google Analytics cookies do not contain any information that personally identifies you. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics visit [ _http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout_](http://t.signaledue.com/e1t/c/5/f18dQhb0S7lC8dDMPbW2n0x6l2B9nMJW7t5XYg4Xr0_CW2BgXCY8q-qn6W7dKLV856dFPWf1ZPm9T02?t=http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout&si=6118029987938304&pi=e3dd71cb-d2e4-4500-97f5-1ac82039fb60). 

**Security   **

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.  We also use encryption technology and a firewall in an attempt to protect information against unlawful intrusions; however, **Ingram cannot guarantee complete security, as it does not exist on the Internet.**   It is important for you to also protect yourself against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished and when using a shared computer.

**Links to Other Sites**  
This Site may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that Ingram is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of such other web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy practices may differ from ours.

**Updates to This Policy   **  
If Ingram decides to change or update this Privacy Policy, it will post those changes and updates on this page so that the User is always aware of what information Ingram collects, how it uses that information, and under what circumstances Ingram discloses it. Ingram encourages each User to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so Users will know if the Privacy Policy has been updated or amended. If you have any questions about the Ingram Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [_websupport@ingramcontent.com_](mailto:legal@ingramcontent.com) or if you have any legal questions, we can be reached at: [_legal@ingramcontent.com_](mailto:legal@ingramcontent.com).
